A Guide to the Office of the Vice President for Administration, Office Administrative Files, [1972] 1981-1986
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the Vice President for Administration, University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files [1972] 1981-1986
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-4/1/2.881
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1988 June 29.
Contents List
- SERIES I: General Files
  - Academic Space 1984 Apr-1985 Feb (Box 1)
  - Administration-General 1984 Mar-1986 Jan (Box 1)
  - V-P for Administration-Renovation of Rotunda, etc. 1984 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Computing-SAS 1984 Jun-Oct (Box 1)
  - Administrative Computing-Proposal to Accelerate the UVA Systems Development Plan 1984 Aug-1985 Jan (Box 1)
  - Administrative Computing-Acquisition of Computing 1984 May-Aug (Box 1)
  - Administrative Computing-Statement of Policy on Computers and Telecommunications 1983 Sep (Box 1)
  - Admissions Office-Job Classification Case 1981 (Box 1)
  - Afro-American Affairs Office 1984 May (Box 1)
  - Albemarle County Planning 1983 Nov-1984 Jun (Box 1)
  - Architectural and Engineering Service 1984 Jul-Nov (Box 1)
  - Asbestos File-General 1984 Sep-1985 Jun (Box 1)
  - Administrative Computing-General 1984 May-1985 May (Box 1)
  - Assistant Vice President for Finance-Comptroller's Office 1984 Oct-1985 Jun (Box 1)
  - Assistant Vice President for Finance Overhead Costs 1985 Apr-May (Box 1)
  - Associate Provost for Research 1984 Dec-1985 Jan (Box 1)
  - Athletic Department UVA 1984 Mar-1985 Jun (Box 1)
  - Auditor's Office 1984 Feb-1985 Jun (Box 1)
  - Board of Visitors' Meeting 1985 May (Box 1)
  - Board of Visitors' Meeting, March Meeting 1985 Apr-May (Box 1)
  - Board of Visitors' Meeting, October 4-5 1984 Jun-Oct (Box 2)
  - Board of Visitors' Meeting, 1985 January 1984 Sep-1985 Jan (Box 2)
  - Buck Mountain Reservoir-General 1984 Mar-Jul (Box 2)
  - Budget-General 1983 Nov-1985 Jun (Box 2)
  - Vice President for Administration-Operation Budget 1984-1985 1984 Jan-1985 Apr (Box 2)
  - Cash Balance-General 1985 Feb (Box 2)
  - Governor's 1984-1986 Budget Amendments 1984 Apr (Box 2)
  - Budget Addendum-Operating Budget 1984-1986 1985 Jan-May (Box 2)
  - Operating Budget 1985-1986 1984 Dec-1986 May (Box 2)
  - Budget-Biennial Budget 1984-1986 1983 Mar-1984 Jan (Box 2)
  - Vice President for Administration-Budget Addendum 1984 1983 Oct-1984 Apr (Box 2)
  - Addendum to Budget 1984-1985-General 1983 Dec-1984 Dec (Box 3)
  - Addendum to Budget 1984-1985-V-P for Administration 1984 Mar (Box 3)
  - Addendum to Budget 1984-1985-Comp. and Comm. 1983 Dec-1984 Mar (Box 3)
  - Addendum to Budget 1984-1985-Equal Opportunity 1983 Dec-1984 Jul (Box 3)
  - Addendum to Budget 1984-1985-Materiel Management 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Addendum to Budget 1984-1985-Printing 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Addendum to Budget 1984-1985-Risk Management and Real Estate 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Addendum to Budget 1984-1985-Communications 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Addendum to Budget 1984-1985-General Services Assistant Vice President 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - (Box 3)
  - Addendum to Budget 1984-1985-Addendum 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Summary of 1984-1985 Addendum Proposals-General Services 1984 Feb-May (Box 3)
  - Summary of 1984-1985 Addendum Proposals-Personnel 1983 Dec-1984 Mar (Box 3)
  - Summary of 1984-1985 Addendum Proposals-Police and Security 1983 Dec-1984 Mar (Box 3)
  - Cabell Hall Security 1983 Feb-1984 May (Box 3)
  - Capital Budget Programs-Capital Outlay Reports 1983 Aug-1984 Jun (Box 3)
  - Capital Budget Program Development 1986-1992 1984 Feb-Jul (Box 3)
  - Carruthers Hall Space meeting 1983 Jan-1984 Mar (Box 3)
  - Center for the Study of Higher Education-Summer Workshop 1985 Feb-June (Box 3)
  - Center for the Study of Higher Education-Trip to Washington, Graduate Students 1985 April 1 1985 Mar-Apr (Box 3)
  - Center for Study of Higher Education 1984 Jan-1985 Jun (Box 3)
  - Central Storage 1984 Jul-Oct (Box 3)
  - Charlottesville/Albemarle County Chamber of Commerce-General 1984 Oct (Box 3)
  - Leadership Charlottesville Subcommittee-Pryor Hale 1984 Apr-Oct (Box 3)
  - Charlottesville/Albemarle Employment and Training Commission-GE info 1983 Sep-1985 Jun (Box 3)
  - Charlottesville-Albemarle Metropolitan Planning Organization 1983 Sep-1985 Mar (Box 4)
  - City of Charlottesville-City Relations 1984 Jan-1985 Mar (Box 4)
  - City of Charlottesville-General 1984 Mar-1985 Apr (Box 4)
  - City of Charlottesville-Community Development Office 1984 May-1985 Apr (Box 4)
  - City of Charlottesville-Joint Transit Maintenance Facilities 1983 Jul-1984 Jul (Box 4)
  - Citizen's Committee for City County Cooperation (The 5 Cs) 1984 Aug-1985 May (Box 4)
  - Colgate Darden Graduate School of Business Administration-General 1984 Jul-Sep (Box 4)
  - Commerce School-General 1984 Aug-1985 Jun (Box 4)
  - Commerce School-Faculty Meeting 1984 Jan-1985 May (Box 4)
  - Communications Services-General 1984 Mar-1985 Jun (Box 4)
  - Complaint Procedure 1984 Dec-1985 Apr (Box 4)
  - Conflicts of Interest Seminar Richmond, 1984 October 2 1984 Aug-Oct (Box 4)
  - Construction Management Contract 1984 Apr-Jun (Box 4)
  - Continuing Education Division 1984 Sep-1985 Apr (Box 4)
  - Council of Academic Deans 1984 Sep-1985 Apr (Box 4)
  - Dean of Students 1984 May-1985 Jun (Box 4)
  - Development Office 1984 Mar-Oct (Box 4)
  - Emergency Operations Plan-General 1973 May (Box 4)
  - Employee Health Service Meetings-General 1984 Mar-Oct (Box 4)
  - Equal Opportunity 1984 May-1985 Jun (Box 4)
  - Equal Opportunity-Complaints 1984 Apr-Sep (Box 5)
  - Equal Opportunity Programs-Affirmative Action Plan for Equal Employment Opportunity 1984 Aug-Sep (Box 5)
  - Personnel Office-Executive Compensation Program-Additional Compensation Study Interim Report, Draft 1983 Dec-1984 Jul (Box 5)
  - Executive Development Proposal (top) 1985 Jun-Aug (Box 5)
  - Expenditures by Object Codes, Comparative Analysis 1985 Feb-Apr (Box 5)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences-Senate Meeting 1984 Aug-1985 Jan (Box 5)
  - Food Service Division 1985 Apr (Box 5)
  - Fraternities and Sororities-Ray Hunt Meeting 1982 Oct-1983 Dec (Box 5)
  - General Services-General 1984 Apr-1985 Jun (Box 5)
  - General Services-Communications 1984 Jul-1985 Jun (Box 5)
  - General Services-Advisory Panel on Postsecondary Education 1984 Oct-Dec (Box 5)
  - General Services-Real Estate and Risk Management 1984 Mar-1985 Jun (Box 5)
  - General Services-Travel Services-Contract 1984 Jan-1985 Jun (Box 5)
  - General Services-Material Management 1984 Apr-Aug (Box 5)
  - General Services-Printing 1984 Sep-1985 Jan (Box 5)
  - Governmental and Legislative Relations-General 1984 Apr-1985 May (Box 5)
  - Legislators, 12/10/84 1984 Nov-Dec (Box 5)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences 1984 Jan-1984 Apr (Box 5)
  - Higher Education Strategic Planning Institute 1984 Apr (Box 5)
  - Historic District Landscaping 1983 Nov-1984 Aug (Box 5)
  - Rugby Road Historic District 1983 Jul-1984 Mar (Box 6)
  - Housing Division 1984 Jul-1985 Jun (Box 6)
  - Incubator Space-Milton Airport-General File 1985 Jan (Box 6)
  - Indirect Cost Survey-General 1985 May-Jun (Box 6)
  - Institutional Planning and Studies 1984 Sep-1985 Jan (Box 6)
  - Joint Dispatch Management Board 1983 Dec-1985 Jun (Box 6)
  - Joint Dispatch Center-911 System-General 1984 Jul-1985 Jan (Box 6)
  - By-laws for Joint Dispatch Center 1984 Mar (Box 6)
  - Comprehensive Plan for Lawn and Lawn Advisory Board 1984 Jan-1985 Jun (Box 6)
  - Legal Advisor's Office 1984 Sep-1985 Jun (Box 6)
  - Local Area Network 1984 Jun (Box 6)
  - Material Management-General 1984 Aug-1985 Jul (Box 6)
  - Material Management-Mowing Contract 1984 May-Aug (Box 6)
  - Material Management-Advisory Board 1983 Mar-1984 Aug (Box 6)
  - Medical Center-General 1984 Jul-1985 Jun (Box 6)
  - Miller Center-General File 1985 May (Box 6)
  - Minority Business Enterprise 1984 Jan-1985 Apr (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous 1984 Apr-1985 Jun (Box 7)
  - Morea House Renovation 1983 Jul-1984 Sep (Box 7)
  - Neighborhood Association-Jefferson Park 1984 Jun-1985 May (Box 7)
  - Parking and Transportation-General 1984 Jun-1985 Mar (Box 7)
  - Partners of the Americas 1984 Oct-1985 Apr (Box 7)
  - Pavilion III 1985 Apr-Jun (Box 7)
  - Pavilion V 1983 Nov (Box 7)
  - Physical Plant-Renovation of Pavilion IX 1983 Apr-1985 May (Box 7)
  - Personal Computers Task Force Committee 1984 Apr-1985 Jun (Box 7)
  - Personnel Office (new) 1984 Mar-1985 Jun (Box 7)
  - Personnel Office-General-first (old) 1984 Mar-Dec (Box 7)
  - Personnel-Annual Service Awards Program 1985 Feb-May (Box 7)
  - Personnel-Early Retirement Incentives 1983 Nov-1984 Oct (Box 7)
  - Personnel-Suggestion Award Program 1983 Jul-1985 Jun (Box 8)
  - Personnel Office-State Grievance Procedure 1984 Jul-1985 Apr (Box 8)
  - Personnel Administration-Time-Income Trade Off 1983 Dec-1984 Mar (Box 8)
  - Personnel Office-Advisory Committee Strategic Planning 1983 Aug-1984 Oct (Box 8)
  - Personnel Office-Training and Development 1984 Sep-1985 May (Box 8)
  - Physical Plant-Peer Review 1985 Feb-Jun (Box 8)
  - Physical Plant-Advisory Board 1984 Jan-Sep (Box 8)
  - Physical Plant-Current File, 1984-1985 1984 Apr-1985 Jun (Box 8)
  - Physical Plant-Projects and Improvements 1984 Mar-1985 Mar (Box 8)
  - Physical Plant-Quarterly Reports 1984 Nov-1985 Apr (Box 8)
  - Physical Plant-Project Status Report 1984 Jan-May (Box 8)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community 1984 Aug-Oct (Box 8)
  - Vice Presidential Planning Group 1983 Aug-1985 Jun (Box 8)
  - Police Department-General 1983 Jun-1985 Jun (Box 9)
  - President's Office-General 1984 Jun-1985 Mar (Box 9)
  - President's Office-Renovation of Pavilion IV 1983 Nov-1984 Mar (Box 9)
  - President's Office-Pavilion VIII Use 1983 Jun-1985 Apr (Box 9)
  - President's Office-Commonwealth Day 1984 Jul-Sep (Box 9)
  - President's Office-Fall Convocation 1984 Sep-Oct (Box 9)
  - President's retreat 1984 Aug-1985 Apr (Box 9)
  - Printing and Mail Services 1984 Mar-1985 May (Box 9)
  - Program Proposal, 1984-1986 1983 Feb-1984 Jan (Box 9)
  - Provost Goals 1984 Apr-May (Box 9)
  - Property Acquisition 1984 Sep-Dec (Box 9)
  - Provost Office 1984 Jul-1985 Apr (Box 9)
  - Regional Commonwealth Conference-General 1984 Jul-1985 Jan (Box 9)
  - Residential Life Comprehensive Plan 1983 Feb-Dec (Box 9)
  - Risk Management-General 1984 Feb-1985 May (Box 9)
  - Risk Management Insurance, 1984-1985 1983 Aug-1985 Mar (Box 9)
  - Risk Management and Real Estate-General 1984 Oct-1985 Jun (Box 9)
  - Real Estate-Barringer House 1983 Jul-1984 Oct (Box 9)
  - Real Estate-Captain Video Building 1985 May (Box 9)
  - Real Estate-Northern Virginia Office Space Consolidation 1981 May-1983 Mar (Box 10)
  - Real Estate-Pepsi Building 1983 Sep-1985 Apr (Box 10)
  - Real Estate-Building Committee-Acquisition of Valentine-Massie Property 1983 Mar-1984 Mar (Box 10)
  - (Box 10)
  - Self Study Programs 1984 Jan-1985 Mar (Box 10)
  - Senior Executive Institute Advisory Committee-General File 1984 Sep-1985 May (Box 10)
  - Southern Regional Education Board 1984 Dec (Box 10)
  - Staff Meeting, 1985 1984 Jul-1985 Jun (Box 10)
  - Secretary of Administration-Andrew Fogarty 1984 Aug-1985 Jun (Box 10)
  - State Administration and Finance Office 1982 Jun-1983 Nov (Box 10)
  - State-Meeting in Richmond-Secretary Anderson 1983 Nov-1984 Aug (Box 10)
  - State Council of Higher Education 1984 Jul-1985 Jan (Box 10)
  - State-Secretary of Finance-Stuart Connock 1984 Aug (Box 10)
  - State Department of General Services 1984 Oct-1985 Mar (Box 10)
  - State Department of Information Technology 1983 Oct-1985 May (Box 10)
  - State Publications 1984 Jul-1985 Jul (Box 10)
  - Summer Session Office 1984 Aug-1985 May (Box 10)
  - Team International 1984 Oct-1985 Feb (Box 11)
  - Transportation Systems-Automated 1985 Mar-May (Box 11)
  - Special Projects--$10,000 Allotment, 1984-1985 1984 May-Sep (Box 11)
  - Systems Planning Committee 1983 May-1985 Apr (Box 11)
  - United Way 1984 Jun-1985 Jun (Box 11)
  - University Policies and Procedures Manual-General File 1984 Oct-1985 Feb (Box 11)
  - Vice President and Provost 1983 Dec-1985 Apr (Box 11)
  - Vice President for Business and Finance 1984 Jan-1985 May (Box 11)
  - Vice President for Development and University Relations 1984 Oct-1985 Apr (Box 11)
  - Vice President for Health Affairs 1985 May (Box 11)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institution-General 1984 Jan-Oct (Box 11)
- SERIES II: Committee Files
  - Administrative Committee 1985 Mar-Jun (Box 11)
  - Advisory Committees-Administration 1984 Jun-Sep (Box 11)
  - Arboretum and Landscape Committee 1984 Aug-1985 Apr (Box 11)
  - Arboretum Committee 1983 Dec-1984 Aug (Box 11)
  - Landscape Steering Committee 1984 Jan (Box 11)
  - Building Committee-Alderman/Stadium Road Housing 1982 Oct-1984 Sep (Box 11)
  - Building Committee-Alderman Library 1983 Aug (Box 11)
  - Building Committee-Heating Plant Expansion 1983 Jan-1985 Mar (Box 11)
  - Building Committee-JAG School Addition 1982 Oct-1985 Jul (Box 11)
  - Building Committee-Monroe Addition 1982 Sep-1985 Jan (Box 11)
  - Building Committee-North Grounds Recreation Committee 1982 Sep-1984 Jul (Box 12)
  - Building Committee-Sports Arena, UVA 1983 Feb-1984 Aug (Box 12)
  - Energy Conservation Committee 1984 Dec-1985 Mar (Box 12)
  - The Educational and Employment Opportunities, Obligations and Rights Committee 1972 Apr-1984 Jun (Box 12)
  - Replacement Hospital-General 1985 Mar-Jun (Box 12)
  - Replacement Hospital Project 1984 Apr-1985 Mar (Box 12)